foreign
manic come take a look at this no me and
my green bro are going into the kitchen
to film a tick tock so we can become
rich like ninja from twitch.com
Now give me your phone so I can film
manic pooping in the sink
sorry I can't right now I'm too busy
looking up haunted locations around town
why are you doing that
well I just figured that since we don't
have any plans for Halloween it might be
fun to do something together
hey check that out
oh this
the shitty demise of Timothy J heparstan
it sounds like a spooky ghost story
well let's see
Legend says here there was once a man
who went by the name Timothy J heperson
every day after he got off work he would
head down to the local Walmart
where he would pull down his pants and
give random Shoppers a beef stew
like he would fart in their face that's
kind of sexy it was at first but one day
he came across the wrong man
[Applause]
while he was farting down his mouth the
man slapped him across the face
Timothy pooped himself a little bit and
had a heart attack
nobody wanted to revive him not even the
doctors that were supposed to be there
to save him so instead he was left to
die now his body rests in Eastern Grove
where he stalked the grounds
looking for any unsuspecting victims to
suffocate with his rancid gas
voila that sounds awfully bitchin
It also says if you smell beef and
broccoli while you're there run
why be fan broccoli
because that was the last thing he ate
Yoon and come poop
damn there's more Legend has it that if
you fart on his grave he will return
back to the Mortal plane and [ __ ] on
your [ __ ] face
I I think that's enough scary stories
for right now you guys let's go do
something else
oh come on don't tell us your chicken
bro you know it's not real I I'm not
scared then prove it let's all head down
there tonight and you know what I'll
even give you 20 bucks if you can make
it through the night without crapping
your pants
20 butts tonight I uh I don't know about
that
sounds like Easy Money wouldn't you say
big blue
I'll call the guys down while I do that
you go put on some khaki pants I don't
want to see even a slitter of poop poop
showing up on your backside
well here we are Eastern Grove
it's a whole lot darker than you guys
made it out to be just as an FYI if
anyone here happens to be afraid of the
dark ain't no shame in turning around so
where is this Timothy they help us and
lad he better not try anything on my
beach otherwise I'll be very unhappy
Timothy G hippesten didn't he die or
some [ __ ] after ordering Chinese takeout
from the Panda Express he's dead how can
you know this
but Libby were you listening to a single
thing on the drive here no
well anyway hopefully he'll come back to
life soon because last time he locked me
suck his balls for a bowl of orange
chicken and I was really hoping he'd let
me do it again
laughs
nope not over here either just a stupid
[ __ ]
maybe we should go do something else
even though we split up it will take
hours to search a graveyard as big as
Sonic's fat butt
Sonia are you sure this is even the
right address maybe we should call Mama
to pick us up
well if you want we could always try
conducting a seance
a seance will let us make contact with
those who have already passed on into
the spirit plane
I I know what it is I just think it's
stupid and a big waste of time
it couldn't hurt to try come on Knox no
way I'll leave you nerds to that one if
you need me I'll be over there going
poop
do you have toilet paper
but I'll just use this
hey give that back
people will see my butt
[ __ ]
oh
foreign
if there is anybody hit with us please
make your presence known preferably a
white ghost because I have my wallet on
me and I'd rather it not be stolen
wait aren't we supposed to have some
kind of offering or something
oh you're right sorry luckily I always
carry a can of loaded potato soup with
me
ah
if there is anybody hit with us please
make your presence known
oh [ __ ]
Butler b you're not supposed to move it
by yourself
but I didn't do anything
you didn't but that's not possible
unless
Timothy Timothy is here he's mad because
I called him not white
Timothy is that true
have you returned to the immortal plane
from the great beyond
ah my hand is moving on its own quick
grabs and pencil and paper
who are you lots of me tell us your name
damn you
h i
would you look at that he's saying hello
what a kind ghost
[Music]
oh for this I'm out of here
foreign
we've got a celebrity in the house
so uh Mr Hitler what are you here doing
in the states do you come here often
how's the weather been for you lately
bro stop trying to spell out Hitler it's
not funny
I think it's pretty funny
what I'm not doing anything
but put that thought aside does anyone
else besides me smell be fan broccoli
ha I don't smell anything
I've had enough of the sewagey board if
neither of you are going to take this
seriously we'll have to try something
else here bro take this
what is it
it's an EVP detector that Uncle Chuck
bought at a yard sale
he thought it would let him bang some
wicked ghost to chess but he threw it
away and started crying when it called
him old
go give it a whirl while me and Sonia
put this [ __ ] up
you shouldn't talk that way about the
Ouija board manic you're disrespecting
the ghosts do you think I really give a
damn sis my name is manic which means I
am a very medic boy like my hair
oh yeah and find Knuckles while you're
at it we're going to leave soon
a machine that lets you talk to ghosts
there's no way such a thing exists well
since I'm here I might as well give it a
shot where's the harm
it doesn't even work what a piece of
junk I can't see why Uncle Chuck threw
it out
my name is Rodrigo
would you like topaya taco Nino
what what's that
enough games manic if this is your idea
of a stupid prank I'm telling mama
hey Sonic why don't you turn around
don't worry nobody is going to hit you
oh my God
[Music]
the curse the curse is real I have to
warn the others
Sonia manic
where are you oh no did he get you too
please Timothy I mean you know harm
I only came to pay respects that's all I
never meant to do anything more honest
old on my beach Daddy is coming for you
get away from my beach you ghastly demon
return to where you belong before I call
the cops
oh no my beach I tripped come back here
and help me
you little [ __ ] I'm going to whip your
ass when I get my hands on you
phew I think I lost the ghost now I just
have to figure out how to get out of
here
how did you find me this fast
it's not possible no
[Music]
[Laughter]
I can't believe you actually fell for it
you big dumb idiot
huh what is this
nice work you guys but you still owe me
five bucks
huh money well spent I say
will someone please tell me what the
hell is going on here am I missing
something
isn't it obvious that whole story about
Timothy J heparstan we made it up
it was a prank and you fell for it hook
line and sinker you dumbass
but the beef and broccoli I smelled beef
and broccoli in the graveyard
that was just Chinese takeout
and the blood I saw on Knuckles close
that was just ketchup my guy no need to
worry
sure maybe that's all fake but there's
no denying the EVP detector I really did
hear something you can't make that up
oh bro that was just Jose with a
megaphone from our Spanish class
hola Soni
so you mean to tell me this was all one
big joke golly I'm so embarrassed
oh geez I'm sorry [ __ ] you weren't too
scared will you you know Daddy would
never let you truly be In Harm's Way
right
after all where would a sugar daddy be
without his sugar baby
hey guys do you smell that something
tells me we suddenly just got 20 bucks
richer haha
bartelby
um I suppose I might as well
after all the money in your back pockets
are likely stained and I'm not talking
about stain from gut I mean poop
now what are we waiting for my friends
it's still early what save you we go to
Applebee's free breadsticks and pester
on me
so the legend of Eastern Grove turned
out to be a face odd if I'm being honest
I'm kind of disappointed but at the same
time kind of relieved I better [ __ ] I
haven't done that yet today
what do you think you're doing over my
grave I'll give you a [ __ ] be stupid
[Music]
wait that's it
foreign
that makes me so mad
[Music]
let's rip it
foreign
[Music]
I know that we can surely feed them all
you play the game
[Music]
everybody